Ravage is a horror, thriller film directed by Teddy Grennan.
When a nature photographer explains to the Police how she fought her way out of the Watchatoomy
Valley, they dismiss her crazed and violent story as a meth-induced nightmare.
But when they discover that she's telling the truth, it's too late.
Harper, played by Annabelle Dexter-Jones.
Ravener, played by Robert Longstreet.
Mallincrkordt, played by Bruce Dern.
Superintendent Slayton, played by Michael Weaver.
Sheriff Pendergras, played by Ross Partridge.
Billy Harrison, played by Christopher Pinkalla.
Ravage (formerly titled Swing Low) is a 2019 American horror thriller film written and
directed by Teddy Grennan, and starring Annabelle Dexter-Jones and Bruce Dern.
The film explores themes of rape, detective, revenge, murder, decapitation.
The tone is dark and intense.